{
    "id": "4657bd8dc3b94552af6b200b1d217c16",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have been waiting here …………….. 6 o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "095d3b4f783c4c08a39e54ed3a4a3669"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys are playing …………….. the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "28f765bcc37640a581e319e30b3fa922"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is someone ……………… the gate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "964a181c57b24e9c8965d20a4cab1564"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you looking ……………… her like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd19bfc2e1244042bd0c98ea3802b242"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite happy ……………. her result.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2b94e82dc81c46ada1bfc6f65bf8fc66"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am impressed ………………. your work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "417fe6eec3794334bf2a847beb01f4b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have been waiting …………….. ages.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f034c1f344f4e96a0b15aafc9dfc5b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "We may go swimming – it depends ……………. the weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bf65f0366c214a39974d959b625f7bde"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju is anxiously waiting …………… his results.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09e7e368910d4db0ab614860055cb5e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is absorbed ………………. his studies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5574acdcbb3c4f9a948fb84c3ccadb07"
        }
    ]
}